{
    "subject": "resource/Kingdom_of_Saxony",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Saxon_vereinsthaler",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Kingdom of Saxony is Saxon vereinsthaler.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9224591255187988,
            "question": "When was the Saxon vereinsthaler introduced as currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9063099026679993,
            "question": "What was the currency of the Kingdom of Saxony?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8758431673049927,
            "question": "What is a Saxon vereinsthaler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8385714292526245,
            "question": "Was the Saxon vereinsthaler used in any other country besides the Kingdom of Saxony?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.812116801738739,
            "question": "What replaced the Saxon vereinsthaler as the official currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8022785186767578,
            "question": "Were there any denominations of the Saxon vereinsthaler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7877336740493774,
            "question": "What was the value of the Saxon vereinsthaler compared to other currencies of the time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6524792909622192,
            "question": "Can you provide any historical context about the use of the Saxon vereinsthaler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6198254823684692,
            "question": "Are there any collectors who specialize in Saxon vereinsthaler coins or banknotes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5143243670463562,
            "question": "Is there a museum that displays historical examples of the Saxon vereinsthaler?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Kingdom of Saxony is Saxon vereinsthaler.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8803_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any collectors who specialize in Saxon vereinsthaler coins or banknotes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8803_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide any historical context about the use of the Saxon vereinsthaler?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8803_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the value of the Saxon vereinsthaler compared to other currencies of the time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8803_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8803_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8803_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8803_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8803_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8803_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8803_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8803_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8803_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8803_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8803_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}\n\nHere's why:\n\nThe documents mention the following information about the Kingdom of Saxony:\n\n* Currency = Saxon thaler (till 1857)\n* Currency = Saxon vereinsthaler (1857-1873)\n\nThis indicates that the currency of the Kingdom of Saxony is indeed the Saxon Vereinsthaler, which matches the query."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the currency used in the Kingdom of Saxony, including details about the Saxon vereinsthaler replacing the Thaler. This supports the statement that the Saxon vereinsthaler was the currency of the Kingdom of Saxony."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}